

Software Engineer

Contact Info



404-987-8881



Los Angeles, CA 90041



reburke286@gmail.com www.beccacodes.com



LinkedIn: @beccaburke



Github: @reburke286

BECCA BURKE

After graduating from UCLA's Full Stack Web Dev Intensive I am excited to find full time work as a Software Engineer. What sets me apart from other junior developers is my professional experience. For the past 8 years I have managed 2 successful coffee shops. I have tremendous work ethic, initiative, and the ability to get along with anyone.

Core Skills

Languages: HTML5, CSS/Bootstrap, Javascript/jQuery Databases: MySQL/sequelize, MongoDB/mongoose

Front-End: React, Handlebars

Back-End: Node.js, RESTful API's, Ajax

Professional History

Store Manager

Peet's Coffee | 2016-present

- Managed successful coffee shop in Hollywood with team of 15
- Grew sales substantially during FY2020, even during pandemic
- Developed staff while maintaining one of company's lowest turnover rates

Software Engineering Tutor

August 2020 - Present

• Tutoring Bootcamp students, assisting with variety of technologies to help them with their projects and class assignments

Front End Designer

UCLA Art Dept | April 2020 - August 2020

• Using Sketch, Jekyll, and Bootstrap I created the front end template frameworks for the new art dept website

Software Engineer Intern

Spokeo | March 2020 - May 2020

- Worked with a team of 3 to build the back end framework for Spokeo's new Chrome Extension
- Custom built a web scraper using RegEx
- Helped build back end in React



BECCA BURKE

Contact Info



404-987-8881



Los Angeles, CA 90041



reburke286@gmail.com www.beccacodes.com



LinkedIn: @beccaburke



Github: @reburke286

educational history

UCLA Extension

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp | 9/2019 - 3/2020

- Went from no coding experience to graduating top 2 in my class with an A average (while working full time in my primary job)
- Completed projects for a software company, an IT company, and a FinTech company
- Spent time off working on extra-curricular projects

Vassar College

Psychology & Film Production B.A. | 8/2004 - 5/2008

- Double majored with a 3.5 GPA
- Sang in Vassar College Choir all four years
- Elected Senior Class Treasurer, 2007-2008
- Received Dean's Award for service to the school, 2008